Hello everyone, today I am here with my favorite teacher, Ms. Moly, to give you a lesson.
Today we switched to live streaming on Thursday because one of our fans left us a message saying that she always missed our live streaming on the highway on Thursdays.
So we switched to live streaming today.
And tomorrow will be a group date with us, so we will meet you all today.
Have you listened to what Tina said last time?
We will be live streaming on Thursdays at 9 a.m.
If you are interested, you can go and check it out.
If you are interested, you can search for us on Tiktok and follow our official Tiktok account.
You can also follow us on Twitter.
You can also send your work to our email.
Then our C-jun will be at the backstage to review it.
If the review passes, I will let you know.
Now, today is the last live streaming on our foundation course.
Today is the last live streaming on our foundation course.
This is the last live stream of the basic class.
After listening to this lesson,
you will graduate from the basic class.
Today,
we are still using the link we got
to find our materials.
If you don't have our materials,
you can reply to the link in the background of our WeChat official account
to get the materials.
First, let's open up the A material.
This is a men's jacket.
Today, we are mainly talking about matching.
I can hear a dog barking.
This fan, your ears are too thick.
You can see this kind of clothing.
Let's open it up and simulate it.
We can see that
it keeps shaking,
including the back.
There are some shaking and twisting.
Let's stop the simulation.
First, we need to determine
what causes this kind of twisting.
For example,
in the sleeve and the back of the sleeve,
we can determine that
this kind of twisting is caused by the sewing line.
For example,
in the front door,
there is a layer of multiple sheets.
So the problem here is
due to the unevenness of the layers.
Now, let's first
change the sewing line direction.
First, let's select all the clothing versions
by pressing Ctrl-A.
Then, press Ctrl-H
or press the hard key.
After the hard key is pressed,
we can simulate it.
Then, let's highlight the uneven parts.
Here, let's select the sewing line tool.
We can also select the fast line B.
Then, let's select the sewing line here.
We can see the sewing line in the 2D window.
We can see that it is in the twisting state.
We can press the right button on the sewing line
to switch the sewing line.
After the sewing line is switched,
we can simulate it.
Now, we can see that
the sewing line is flat here.
It is no longer moving.
Now, let's turn the sewing line to the back.
We can also select the sewing line here.
We can see the sewing line
in the twisting state.
As you can see,
the sewing line here is a little bit more.
Then, we can select the sewing line
and drag it down to the right place.
Then, we can simulate it again.
We can see that it is still moving.
It means that there is more than one sewing line here.
After selecting the sewing line,
if you don't know how to solve it,
we can select the sewing line
and delete it.
Press Ctrl-A to delete it.
After deleting the sewing line,
wait for it to be flat.
Then, we can sew it again.
After that,
we can sew it together.
Notice the direction of the sewing line.
Don't do it the other way around.
Okay.
The unevenness of the sewing line here
has been removed.
Now, let's see
the unevenness of the sewing line here.
The unevenness here
is mainly because it has many layers.
There is a gap between the layers.
Then, here,
we need to reset the layers.
We can select the Android system.
Select the Android system.
Select all the files in the front door.
After selecting all of them,
press the button again
to reset the 2D arrangement position.
After selecting the 2D arrangement position,
then,
we can adjust the 2D arrangement position.
First, this is a box.
So, it should be at the bottom.
Then, we can use the positioning ball tool
to arrange it like this.
Let's see the arrangement of the 2D arrangement.
When you are arranging,
you need to pay attention
to the layers between them.
There is not much gap
but there is a certain distance to be kept.
After arranging this part
After arranging,
let's arrange the two curves.
You can also use the positioning tool to arrange them.
After that, we will arrange the two doors on the right side
We can use the shortcut to arrange the doors
After arranging the doors, we can use Shift-F to open the arrangement
Select the front panel and place it on the arrangement
After placing it on the arrangement, we can use the locator to move it a little
So that it moves away from the front window
After placing it closer to the front window, we can open the arrangement again
Now the front door won't move again
There is a silly girl who said she didn't see the arrangement
I can show you again
When we select any of the panels
In the upper right corner of the locator, there is a cross mark
Click on the cross mark
You will see a grey mark
Click on the panel that you need to arrange
Click on it
You can see the original panel is arranged on the top of the panel that we just selected
Now the panel is arranged
This is our quick arrangement
Now we will open the door
And we are ready to go
Now the colder clothe is stable
Except the bottom part
Now we will move to the next part
The whole clothing curve
No need to write
This is a lady's dress.
Let's open the model.
We can see that the front is shaking.
Let's put it back to its original state.
Like this.
Let's do the same thing as before.
Select the top part of the model.
Then press Z to re-arrange the 2D position.
This is the front.
You can use the quick arrangement tool.
Then use the locator to create a layer gap.
The same goes for the other model.
Push it in.
Press Z to re-arrange the 2D position.
After that, let's give the front a layer gap.
Select the right front.
Use the locator to place it on top of the left front.
Like this.
A layer gap.
You can see it.
After arranging,
select the front part of the model.
Press Z to re-arrange the 2D position.
Then press Z to place it on top of the left front.
After placing it on top of the left front,
you can see that there is a layer gap.
After arranging, close the top part of the model.
The top part is done.
Let's do the bottom part of the model.
Follow only one layer step.
And place it on top of the right front.
UNIVERSE
Passed the top part of the model to the left bottom.
And then to the top.
Press Z to retract the view.
Press Z to look like a left-hand.
Dream and H communicating.
You can also use the locator to move it.
Open the simulation again.
The costume is done.
Don't forget to change the fabric and shape of the model.
The dress is done.
Next,
What should we do when the button is unstable?
This is a file.
When we open the simulation,
we can see that the button and the front door are deformed.
What should we do here?
First, we can see that it is an unorganized layer.
We can click on it.
We can click on this door.
Then use the locator to pull it out.
After that,
we can use the 3D tool in the tool bar.
Select the move button tool.
Then select all the buttons in the 2D tool bar.
After selecting all the buttons,
click on the first button to reset the 3D position.
Then open the simulation.
There is still the last one.
What should we do?
We can remove it first.
Hold down the command Started.
Click on it.
Then press down the command.
Hold the command,
and press out the key.
The video will be restyled.
How about this?
It is still very first.
Can we brew it?
We need to create a new video.
Let's try.
We need to create one new video.
Once.
It will start to play like this.
What should we do?
After that, we choose the one with the button and buttonhole on it.
Press it, and then use the shortcut to move it to the top of the front door.
This is a more efficient way to move the button.
What is the shortcut to move back and forth?
The shortcut is Ctrl-Z.
The shortcut to move back and forth is Ctrl-Z.
I still remember the sound from the previous live stream.
Do you play the same piano as me on livesames?
Then you can 0-3408 this number,
0-3408 this number,
Next, we are going to do a video about the wrong way to adjust your sleeves when you are styling.
Is it about your eyes? Yes, it's about my eyes.
I didn't expect you guys to remember about my eyes.
Last time, we were laughing our heads off.
3400, you said you know Tina.
Yes, I do.
Let's go back to the video.
This is how a sleeve looks like.
The sleeve is a bit narrow.
After opening the model, we can see that some parts are not in the right place.
Some parts are in the wrong place.
The sleeve is in the model's hands.
You guys are so vicious.
How to fix this?
We can take the sleeve back to the original state.
We can use the sleeve to adjust the sleeve.
We can place the button on the sleeve, and we'll have a locator tool here.
We can use the blue circle to rotate the locator,
and pass the sewing line through the arm.
This 999 says it's a golden hair.
Yes, you have to pay attention.
If you don't know how to use the locator,
you can check out our previous live stream.
Do you still remember the last time we played hide-and-seek,
and how I laughed at Little Sui Jin?
We can use the locator tool to rotate the first one.
The other way is,
we can use the locator tool to rotate it,
and then move it.
We can see the sewing line here,
we have to pass it through.
Let's open the model again.
Now the sleeve is done, right?
This is one of the solutions.
Let's open it again.
The first one is the first way,
and the second one is the third way.
Let's open the second one.
The second one is 3D tool.
The third one is the select grid tool.
We select the grid tool,
and we can use the grid tool to select the grid here.
We can see the selected grid is green,
Press SHIFT to select the other side as well.
You can see that the grid has been selected.
After selecting the grid, click on the green grid.
Use the positioning tool to pull out the grid.
Open the model again.
The arm is now out.
The other side is the same.
Select the grid.
If you have too many options, you can press CTRL and select the grid.
The grid selection will be cancelled.
Use the positioning tool to pull out the grid.
The arm is done.
Thank you for watching.
See you next time.
Here is our
today's topic.
Let me show you how to make the waistband of a gold pair of pants
This is a pair of pants. Let's make the waistband
First of all, let's make the waistband a front waistband
and make some adjustments
You can check out the previous video
This is the front waistband
The front waistband is not folded
So you can sew it up
After that, let's make the back waistband
There is a waistband inside the back waistband
How to make this waistband?
There are two layers of the waistband
There is a elastic band in the middle
This is the back waistband
Right click
Go to the inner layer of the clothes
You can see there is a waistband in the middle
Make the layers bigger
And the elastic band
Use the fastener
Use the positioning tool to push it to the middle of the two layers
Then we start to sew it up
After sewing it up, we select the elastic band and the waistband
This is the elastic band to the waist band
In the parallel machine
Change the elastic band type to Tune
After sewing it up, we sew the waistband to the pants
When sewing here, be careful to press Shift
And then press Shift
Then press Shift
After that, we will choose the back of the three pieces and make the whole arrangement for it.
This is how it should look like.
I forgot to add a button on the front
After you're done, don't forget to add the
The most important step is to add the
The lining. I've added it here
After you're done, you can
Open it up and simulate it
Let me adjust the position a little bit.
Remember to reduce the particle diameter here.
Let's turn it to the other side first.
And then simulate it.
If you see a floating layer like this,
you can set a layer for it.
We can move the inner layer
to the lower layer,
and the outer layer to the lower layer.
Just confirm it.
Let's open the simulation again.
Then stir it well.
See the layer is stable,
and we can set the layer to 0.
That's it.
You also need to reduce the density of the particles.
But if you don't like the result, you can reduce the amount of particles.
And you're done.
Now I'm going to make a white shirt.
You can check out our previous video about details.
It's about a white skirt.
Maybe it's similar to your white shirt.
The designer is a chef.
You can check out our previous video about details.
The next one is the most important one.
You guys have been waiting for this one for a long time.
Every time we do a live stream,
we get a question about how to make your own shoes.
How to make your own shoes.
Do you guys want to see how to make your own shoes?
We recorded a video about how to make your own shoes.
You can check it out.
You can check out our previous video about details.
We recorded a video about how to make your own shoes.
This is the shoe we made.
You can put it in the animation.
这样子比较社会。
We would like to recognize our friendly H輿理模特 Notice the profile.
We need to anchor ourさ spl storm.
Today's H輿理模特 We do have our Radical H Jon,
which is 정도 medical opiine.
Here is S title.
Please enter the göre and pht with these three.
S t t Many sweet.
Any more Hs that.
Any more h.
Click OK.
Now we can import the model to other software.
We import the model to other software to make it easier for us to find its location.
Now we select 3D model from the window.
Press Alt and Shift at the same time
and press 4 keys.
Then press Alt and Shift at the same time.
And press Alt and Shift at the same time.
and change the type of the model to a shoe
In the model ID list,
We can choose the type we want based on the selection in the image.
Then we can find the location of the file we just created.
You can also add a
Click Save.
It's done.
手按不到那么多键,让我妈帮我按一下。I can't press so many keys, let my mom press them for me.
I can't press so many keys, let my mom press them for me.
The result is that the speed is not too fast.
I can now choose to switch to some color,
and then check only with actions to check the words.
I'm going to add a new layer to the top layer.
When the shoe is bent,
we can choose the weight of the shoe,
and press the button below to adjust the division value.
Ctrl-L, Shift-F
Again, Merci P Whole
And back to the
Today's Epic
People
If you like this video, please like, comment, and subscribe to my channel, and don't forget to turn on the notification bell to be notified when I upload a new video.
This is the end of this video.
If you don't understand what I'm talking about, please stay tuned for my next video.
In this video, I'm going to show you how to turn your shoes into clothes.
If you want to know how to make shoes, please stay tuned.
I'm going to show you how to turn your shoes into clothes in my next video.
This pair of shoes is made from other modeling software.
Do you have any questions?
This is the end of this video.
Thank you for watching.
If you have any questions, please let me know.
This is the end of this video.
Please follow my WeChat official account.
I'll upload a video regularly.
I'll post a video on the WeChat official account.
I'll post a video of my face on June 19.
I'll post a video on June 19.
Ah, I have a problem with my E23.
What happened to it?
I'm using the MD for a long time.
Why aren't you answering me?
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask them in the comment section below.
You will see me again in the future.
Please keep an eye on me.
If you have any further questions, please feel free to ask them in the comment section below.
Lien Yu purchased a forgive 니布 抖洞 waiting room and gave orders to me to confusing my Virtual
hosting site by mostly the original location list.
Do you want to try?
Do you want to see this model again?
This model can be arranged in two ways.
You can also pull out the two layers inside.
The same is to give it a layer arrangement first,
and then simulate it.
You can also stabilize it like this.
Can you show us how to pull it out?
We have just shown you how to pull it out.
I found that Chloe's streamer is cute.
No, all of our streamers are cute.
Isn't our MD Sherry cute?
I really like Sherry.
Come on.
The one who is pulling out the streamer,
we are going to help you talk to me.
What kind of streamer do you want?
How do you arrange the layers in one piece?
What kind of layer do you want?
Do you think there is a layer arrangement between the two pieces?
You can start.
Yes.
How to rotate?
How to rotate video?
Can you show us?
We can fill the file with a video capture and record.
Here you can make our video.
We can set the size of the video.
Here we can set the setting and the direction.
including the rotation direction, duration, and recording.
After recording, you can save the video by clicking save.
I will face each layer to see if the Things coyllum is not cumbersome.
I set the screen full-fledged resolution 5.2.284.
Thank you.
大家还有什么问题吗?
那应该想看抽折的。
你到底想看什么样子的抽折呀?
你到底想看抽折的。
裤子加上衣走秀时,裤子老掉。
裤子老掉?
你裤子要掉的话呢,你可以用我们这个虚拟模特援助胶带,给它胶带一圈。
然后再用贴附到虚拟模特胶带这个上面,选择版片贴附到胶带上面就可以了。
然后再用贴附到虚拟模特胶带这个上面,选择版片就行了。
裤子老掉了,加上胶带说,裤子放进去。
这个你可以使用我们的......
I'm sorry, I forgot to put on my band-aid.
First, check if your belt is sticky.
Why is my shirt so loose?
You can...
Use the glue stick to stick your shoulder line onto the model's shoulder
How to draw a water bottle?
Press Shift to draw a water bottle
Thank you for watching.
The model can put on make-up, but you only need to click on the head of the virtual model,
and there will be a pattern on the side of the screen.
Click on the pattern on the side of the screen,
and you can find the location of the pattern.
Open the pattern, and put it in the PS to make up.
No response.
No response from 7899.
What's your problem?
Maybe there were too many comments, and it was deleted.
I heard a dog barking.
Your ears are so sharp.
I can't hear you clearly.
You can find the depictions of Cololo on Motion.
Check out the other sites if you require it.
The flying coat is so cool.
Yes.
I think it's really cool
Dongge
Dongge sometimes sees your post
Yes, you can send our post to our email
As for some specific operations
We will post them on our WeChat official account
You can check out our WeChat official account
Can you teach me how to do it?
You can check it out later
We have talked about model rotation
You can find it in the main menu
Here is a video capture
There is a rotation recording
You can record it
Please accept the picture
Is everyone ignoring me?
Yes, of course
Is there any problem?
Didn't you ask me if I can teach you how to do it in the future?
We can check it out later
Can you make your own hair?
Yes, the hair is the same as the shoes
It's just that you can change your shoes into your hair
when you insert the shoes
You can see that there is a separation here
Do you have any questions?
If you don't have any questions
We will end the live stream at 9 o'clock
This is our last live stream today
Are you happy?
I'm very happy
Thank you for watching
See you next time
Bye
Remember to watch the live stream about the model rotation
at 8 o'clock next Friday
If you need it, you can check it out
The model rotation page
The basic class is about to graduate
How to put on shoes
I just put the video of shoes in the video
If you haven't seen it just now
You can pay attention to the live stream
at 8 o'clock next Friday
Yes, everyone is graduating from elementary school
You can look forward to the master car behind
Thank you, Molly
Thank you, little cutie
The online software download speed is too slow
No, I don't think so
It may be that your network speed is not very good
You can find one
You can download it with the internet
Don't download it directly from wifi
Where to download the software
You can download it on our official website
Our official website address is
www.close3d.com
You can go to our official website to download it.
What did you buy for 618?
I bought a lot of things.
Are you looking forward to me?
See you init profund.
It also comes with a downloadable version.
要不要看到吗?Do you want to see it?
大家记得期待一下我们可爱的大师直通车 Please look forward to our cute DASHI's直通车
也是大家从第一次我的基础系列开播开始就很期待的一个系列 It's a series that you have been looking forward to since the first time I started my basic series
我期待那个小嘻笑出声 I look forward to that little smiley face
大家上一次机也还没有听过我们的笑声吗? Have you all heard our smiley faces in the last episode?
已经9点01分了 It's already 9.01
在这里我们就要下播了 I hope you all have a good time
也希望大家有一个愉快的中午 I hope you all have a good afternoon
不要忘记明天要上班 Don't forget to go to work tomorrow
我们今天的直播就到这里就结束了 That's it for today's live
大家同样不要忘记来给我们进行投稿哦 Don't forget to subscribe to our channel
拜拜 Bye bye
我们下期再见 Bye bye